Guide to the Minnie Fisher Cunningham Papers 2006-010
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
Minnie Fisher Cunningham Papers
1914-1944
University of Houston Libraries
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
2006-010
9.0 Linear Feet
The Cunningham Papers are divided into 9 series and 10 boxes making up approximately 9 linear feet spanning the years 1914 to 1964. The papers include correspondence, press releases, news clippings, programs, bulletins, speeches, expense accounts, campaign lists, strategic plans and organizational materials.
Biographical Information
Minnie Fisher Cunningham, woman suffrage leader and leading liberal Democrat, the daughter of Horatio White and Sallie Comer (Abercrombie) Fisher, was born on March 19, 1882, on Fisher Farms, near New Waverly, Texas. Her father was a prominent planter who served in the House of Representatives of the Seventh Texas Legislature in 1857-58. He introduced her to politics by taking her to political meetings at Huntsville. After having been educated by her mother, Minnie passed a state examination to earn a teaching certificate when she was sixteen. She taught for a year before enrolling in the University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston. In 1901 she became one of the first women to receive a degree in pharmacy in Texas; she worked as a pharmacist in Huntsville for a year, but she later said that inequity in pay "made a suffragette out of me." In 1902 she married Beverly Jean (Bill) Cunningham, a lawyer and insurance executive. His successful race for county attorney as a reform candidate was her first taste of the campaign trail, but the marriage was unhappy, in part because of her increasing political activity and his alcoholism.
The Cunninghams moved to Galveston in 1907. By 1910 she was elected president of the Galveston Equal Suffrage Association and toured Texas to speak for the cause. In 1915 she was elected to the first of four annual terms as president of the Texas Woman Suffrage Association (subsequently the Texas Equal Suffrage Association). The number of local auxiliaries quadrupled during her first year in office, largely because of her leadership. In 1917 she moved to Austin, opened state suffrage headquarters near the Capitol, and began a campaign that culminated in legislative approval for woman suffrage in state primary elections in 1918.
In 1919 Carrie Chapman Catt, president of the National American Woman Suffrage Association, persuaded Minnie Cunningham to lobby Congress for the Nineteenth Amendment. When the amendment finally was passed and submitted to the states for ratification, Cunningham said she "pursued governors all over the west" and urged them to ratify it. That same year, she helped organize the National League of Women Voters and became its executive secretary. Twenty years later Eleanor Roosevelt recalled that Cunningham's address at the league's second annual convention made her feel "that you had no right to be a slacker as a citizen, you had no right not to take an active part in what was happening to your country as a whole."
Minnie Cunningham was widowed in 1927 and traveled to Texas to settle her husband's estate. The following year she became the first Texas woman to run for the United States Senate. She challenged Earle B. Mayfield, the incumbent, with a platform that advocated prohibition, tariff reduction, tax reform, farm relief, flood control, cooperation with the League of Nations, and opposition to the Ku Klux Klan. She finished fifth of six in the primary, carrying only her home county, Walker. She then campaigned for Thomas T. Connally, the runner-up, who edged out Mayfield in the runoff.
From 1930 to 1939 Cunningham worked in College Station as an editor for the Texas A&M Extension Service. She returned to Washington in 1939 to work as an information specialist for the Women's Division of the Agricultural Adjustment Administration. President Franklin Delano Roosevelt is credited with having given her the nickname by which she later became widely known, "Minnie Fish." She resigned in 1943 to protest a rule impeding the flow of information to farmers.
In 1944, at the Democratic state convention, anti-Roosevelt forces elected "uninstructed" delegates to the national convention, effectively disenfranchising the voters of Texas. Outraged, Roosevelt supporters elected their own slate of delegates at a rump convention. When a coalition of liberal Democrats failed to draft J. Frank Dobie as a candidate for governor, Cunningham ran herself. Angry that the incumbent governor, Coke Stevenson, did not take a public stand on the split, she ran an outspoken campaign, calling on Stevenson to declare his views, and prevented his leading the anti-Roosevelt delegation to the national convention. Stevenson won the primary by a landslide. Nevertheless, in a field of nine candidates, Cunningham finished second.
In 1946 she retired to Fisher Farms in New Waverly to raise cattle and pecans, but she continued to campaign for the Democratic party and organized ad hoc committees to support liberal causes. When the board of regents fired the president of the University of Texas, Homer P. Rainey, she opposed the regents' decision and supported Rainey's unsuccessful bid for the governorship. In the wake of the Supreme Court ruling in Brown vs. Board of Education she supported civil rights on her local school board. In 1952 she stumped for Adlai Stevenson for president and Ralph Yarborough for governor. Prepared to mortgage her farm to ensure the continuation of a liberal voice in Texas journalism, she played a pivotal role in founding the Texas Observer in 1954. Also in the 1950s she helped start Democrats of Texas, an organization of liberals. In 1960, at the age of seventy-eight, she managed the campaign headquarters for John F. Kennedy in New Waverly. Minnie Cunningham died on December 9, 1964, and was buried in New Waverly.
BIBLIOGRAPHY:
Minnie Fisher Cunningham Papers, Houston Metropolitan Research Center, Houston Public Library. John Carroll Eudy, "The Vote and Lone Star Women: Minnie Fisher Cunningham and the Texas Equal Suffrage Association," East Texas Historical Journal 14 (Fall 1976). Patricia B. Nieuwenhuizen, Minnie Fisher Cunningham and Jane Y. McCallum: Leaders of Texas Women (Senior thesis, University of Texas at Austin, 1982). Notable American Women: A Biographical Dictionary (4 vols., Cambridge, Massachusetts: Harvard University Press, 1971-80). Texas Observer, November 21, 1958. Vertical Files, Barker Texas History Center, University of Texas at Austin.
Patricia Ellen Cunningham
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Related Materials
Minnie FisherCunningham: The McArthur-Smith Research Papers, Minnie Fisher Cunningham Digital Collection
Digital Collections
Minnie Fisher Cunningham Papers digital collection (http://digital.lib.uh.edu/collection/p15195coll33)
Scope and Contents
The Cunningham Papers are divided into 9 series and 10 boxes making up approximately 9 linear feet spanning the years 1914 to 1964. The papers include correspondence, press releases, news clippings, programs, bulletins, speeches, expense accounts, campaign lists, strategic plans and organizational materials.
These materials document Mrs. Cunningham's heavy involvement in the National American Woman Suffrage Association, the Texas Equal Suffrage Association, other state suffrage associations, politics, political campaigns, anti-vice, labor, war efforts, Democratic Party Activity plus documentation of her activities in later years.
Perhaps of most interest is a collection of suffrage material from each county of Texas during 1918 & 1919. This is a very important time for the Texas Equal Suffrage Association in particular as it culminated in legislative approval for woman suffrage in state primary elections in 1918 and in universal woman suffrage in 1920.
Women -- Political activity -- Texas -- Houston; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Records (documents); Speeches (documents)
- National American Woman Suffrage Association (NAWSA) Activity, 1915-1920
  - General correspondence, 1915-1916 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters from Carrie Chapman Catt, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters from Carrie Chapman Catt, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters from Carrie Chapman Catt, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Carrie Chapman Catt, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Carrie Chapman Catt, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission - correspondence, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission - correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Woman Citizen - correspondence relating to subscriptions and information for publication, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - National Woman Suffrage Publishing Company - general correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Press releases and bulletins, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Press releases and bulletins, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Press releases and bulletins, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Press releases and bulletins, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Press releases, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Constitution, suffrage publications, outlines, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Suffrage campaign material, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Convention programs, reports, songs, ballot, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Convention programs, reports, addresses, 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - National suffrage organizations - Literature, Men's League for Woman Suffrage; miscellaneous printed materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Various Suffrage Activity, 1917-1918; undated
  - Printed speeches on woman suffrage, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Photographs - Mrs. B. Burke and Miss R. Richardson, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Suffrage clippings - national, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Suffrage clippings - Congressional consideration of federal amendment, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Record of Congressional voting - federal amendment; Presidential suffrage friends and enemies, Jan. 10, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - State Suffrage Associations - Alabama, Arkansas, California - correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - State Suffrage Associations - Florida, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Louisiana - Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - State Suffrage Associations - Massachusetts, Michigan, Missouri - correspondence, press releases, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - State Suffrage Associations - New York, Oklahoma - correspondence, press releases, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - State Suffrage Associations - South Dakota, Virginia, West Virgina, Wisconsin - correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Suffrage clippings, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Texas Equal Suffrage Association - General Correspondence "A" "B", 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Texas Equal Suffrage Association (TESA) Activity, 1915-1920
  - Legislative Report; List of Board Members; Constitution, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Lists of Suffrage literature; Miscellaneous lists, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Clippings, primarily concerning county suffrage efforts, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Clippings, primarily concerning local suffrage efforts, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Headquarters Expenditures, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Financial Statements, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, newspapers, The Dallas News, Galveston News, Houston Chronicle, Houston Post, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, newspapers, relating to distribution of suffrage supplement, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence and records, newspapers, relating to distribution of Texas Democrat, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper records by county; correspondence, Texas Press Clippings Bureau, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Clippings - Galveston News, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Clippings - Houston Chronicle, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Clippings - Houston Post, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Circular Letters, 1915-1916 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Circular Letters, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Circular Letters, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Circular Letters, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Circular Letters, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Federal suffrage amendment efforts, general correspondence, circular letters, December 1917 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Federal suffrage amendment efforts, general correspondence, circular letters, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Federal suffrage amendment efforts, telegrams, January 1918 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Federal suffrage amendment efforts, miscellaneous correspondence, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Federal suffrage amendment efforts, correspondence, May 1919 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Federal suffrage amendment, ratification, correspondence, June 1919 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - General correspondence relating to Texas constitutional amendment referendum, May 1919 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - General correspondence relating to legislative efforts to amend election laws, June 1919 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous materials relating to campaigns for federal and state suffrage amendments, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Information concerning congressional districts and Texas congressmen, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Clippings concerning federal and State Suffrage amendments, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Primary Suffrage, general correspondence, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Primary Suffrage, materials, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Primary Suffrage, correspondence relating to the injunction to prevent Texas women from voting, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Primary Suffrage, clippings relating to threatened injunction and to voter registration, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Vernice W. Reppert, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Vernice W. Reppert, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Anna J. Pennybacker, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Jesse Daniel Ames, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, pamphet; contract, Donna Roberts, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Hortense Ward, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Clippings and photographs - Hortense Ward, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and materials relating to Mississippi Valley Conference; Correspondence relating to Chautaugua, 1917; 1918 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, materials relating to state conferences, May 1915; May 1916; May 1917; May 1918; October 1919 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Report; Outline of the History of Woman Suffrage in Texas, Sept. 1, 1916 - November 1, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Suffrage lists, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Suffrage resolutions, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous materials, notes, unidentified correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1915-1919
    - Eleanor Brackenridge, 1917-1920 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "C", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Anna B. Cade, 1916-1919 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Belle C. Crichett, El Paso; 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - "D", 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. John Davis, concerning finances of organization, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "E", 1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "F", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "G", 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Lena Gardner, Ft. Worth, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Rena Maverick Green, San Antonio, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Wilhelmina M. Guerard, Houston, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - "H", 1915-1918 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Francis E. Heafer, Amarillo; Kate Hunter, Palestine, 1916-1918 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - "J", 1917 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - "K", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - "L", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - "M", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - "Mc", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Jane McCallum, Austin; Elizabeth Maury, San Antonio, 1917-1918; 1926 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - "N", 1917 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - "P", 1916-1918 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Elizabeth Herndon Potter, concerning federal amendment and personal to MFC, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Elizabeth Herndon Potter, concerning federal amendment and personal to MFC, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - "Q", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - "R", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - "S", 1917 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - "S", 1918 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - "T", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - "U-V", 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "W", 1916-1919 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Writer's Bureau, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - "Y-Z", 1917 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Austin Association, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Dallas Association, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - El Paso Association, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Houston Association, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Huntsville and Laredo Associations, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - San Marcos and Waco Associations, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Reports and Correspondence, Counties, 1918-1919
    - Anderson County; Andrews County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Angelina County; Aransas County; Archer County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Armstrong County; Atascosa County; Austin County; Bailey County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Bandera County; Bastrop County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Baylor County; Bee County; Bell County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Bexar County; Blanco County; Borden County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Bosque County; Bowie County; Brazoria County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Brazos County; Brewster County; Briscoe County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Brooks County; Brown County; Burnet County; Caldwell County; Calhoun County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Callahan County; Cameron County; Camp County; Carson County; Cass County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Castro County; Chambers County; Cherokee County; Childress County; Clay County; Cochran County; Coke County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Coleman County; Collin County; Collingsworth County; Colorado County; Comal County; Comanche County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Concho County; Cooke County; Coryell County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Cottle County; Crane County; Crockett County; Crosby County; Culberson County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Dallam County; Dallas County; Dawson County; Deaf Smith County; Delta County; De Witt County; Dickens County; Dimmit County; Donley County, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Duval County; Eastland County; Ector County; Edwards County; Ellis County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - El Paso County; Erath County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Falls County; Fannin County; Fayette County; Fisher County; Floyd County; Foard County; Fort Bend County; Franklin County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Freestone County; Frio County; Gaines County; Galveston County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Garza County; Gillespie County; Glasscock County; Goliad County; Gonzales County; Gray County; Grayson County; Gregg County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Grimes County; Guadalupe County; Hale County; Hall County; Hamilton County; Hansford County; Hardeman County; Hardin County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Harris County; Harrison County; Hartley County; Haskell County; Hays County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Hemphill County; Henderson County; Hidalgo County; Hill County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Hockley County; Hood County; Hopkins County; Houston County; Howard County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Hunt County; Jack County; Jackson County; Jasper County; Jeff Davis County; Jefferson County; Jim Hogg County; Jim Wells County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Johnson County; Jones County; Karnes County; Kaufman County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Kendall County; Kent Count; Kerr County; Kimble County; King County; Kinney County; Kleberg County; Knox County; Lamar County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Lamb County; Lampasas County; La Salle County; Lavaca County; Lee County; Leon County; Liberty County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Limestone County; Lipscomb County; Live Oak County; Llano County; Loving County; Lubbock County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Lynn County; McCulloch County; McLennan County; McMillan County; Madison County; Marion County; Martin County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Mason County; Matagorda County; Maverick County; Medina County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Menard County; Midland County; Milam County; Mills County; Mitchell County; Montague County; Montgomery County; Moore County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Morris County; Motley County; Nacogdoches County; Navarro County; Newton County; Nolan County; Nueces County; Ochiltree County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Oldham County; Orange County; Palo Pinto County; Panola County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Parker County; Parmer County; Pecos County; Polk County; Potter County; Presidio County; Rains County; Randall County; Reagan County; Real County; Red River County; Reeves County; Refugio County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Roberts County; Robertson County; Rockwall County; Runnels County; Rusk County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Sabine County; San Augustine County; San Patricio County; San Saba County; San Jacinto County; Schleicher County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Scurry County; Shackelford County; Shelby County; Sherman County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Smith County; Somervell County; Starr County; Stephens County; Sterling County; Stonewall County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sutton County; Swisher County; Tarrant County; Taylor County; Terrell County; Terry County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Throckmorton County; Titus County; Tom Green County; Travis County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Tyler County; Trinity County; Upshur County; Upton County; Uvalde County; Val Verde County; Van Zandt County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Victoria County; Walker County; Waller County; Ward County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Washington County; Webb County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Wharton County; Wheeler County; Wichita County; Wilbarger County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Willacy County; Williamson County; Wilson County; Winkler County; Wise County; Wood County; Yoakum County; Young County; Zapata County; Zavalla County, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Organizational Materials, undated
    - Outline for County Campaign; Lists of County Chairmen; Suffrage Associations by Counties; Record of County Population, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - County Chairmen, Texas Democrat; List of addresses; Status of County Chairmen; Mailing list; Senatorial District List, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Lists of state newspapers; Lists of Men Supporting Suffrage; List of Texas Women interested in "Forward Movements"; Misc. lists, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - City lists of Men opposed to Suffrage amendment, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - County lists of Men Opposed to State Suffrage amendment, Armstrong-Floyd, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - County lists of Men Opposed to State Suffrage amendment, Hale-Lubbock, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - County lists of Men Opposed to State Suffrage amendment, Martin-Pecos, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - County lists of Men opposed to state suffrage amendment, Patten-Wheeler, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Lists regarding distribution of literature, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - State Advisory Committee; Texas Senatorial Districts; Senatorial District Chairmen; Mailing list, Ratification committee; Mailing list, City presidents, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)